1    May God arise and may his foes be scattered far and put to  flight. As smoke is blown before the wind so may your foes be blown from sight. As wax is melted by the fire may they before God's wrath expire. 

2    But may the righteous all be glad; may they rejoice and sing aloud. Sing praise to God, sing to his name; extol the One who rides the cloud. For he alone is named the LORD  – with joy all praise to him accord. 



