1    The fool speaks in his heart; “There is no God,” he says. They are corrupt, their deeds are vile; none walk in godly ways. The LORD looks down from heaven upon the human race to see if any understand, if any seek God’s face. 

2    They all have turned aside; corrupt they have become. Not one of them does any good – no, not a single one. Will sinners never learn? My people they’ve devoured as if they were consuming bread; they never seek the LORD. 

3    But see that evil crowd! They are struck down with dread, although they thought within their hearts they would have ease instead. The bones of all your foes were scattered far abroad; and you have put them all to shame; they were despised by God. 

