1    Lord, you have been our dwelling place through all the ages of our race. Before you gave the mountains birth or formed and fashioned all the earth, from years which no beginning had to years unending, you are God! 

2    You turn man back to dust again; you say, “Return to dust, O men!” For in your sight a thousand years like yesterday, when past, appears; a thousand years are in your sight brief as a portion of the night. 

3    You with a flood have swept men on, so like a sleep they're quickly gone. They're like the grass which quickly grows— each morning its new growth it shows; though green beneath the morning sun, it's withered ere the day is done. 

