1    O sing ye hallelujah! 'Tis good our God to praise; 'tis pleasant and becoming to him our songs to raise. He builds the walls of Zion, he seeks her wandering sons; he binds their wounds and comforts the brokenhearted ones. 

2    The starry hosts he numbers, he calls them all by name; his greatness and his wisdom his wondrous works proclaim. The meek he lifts to honour, he humbles sinful pride. Give thanks to him and utter his praises far and wide. 



