1    O my God, do not keep silent; be not quiet, be not still. See how all your foes are stirring, eager to move in and kill. For they plot against your loved ones, make their cunning plans, and say, “Come, let us destroy their nation; Israel’s name we’ll sweep away.” 

2    With one mind they plot against you; they are allies for the fight – tents of Hagar and of Moab, Edom and the Ishmaelite, Gebal, Amalek and Ammon, Philistines with men of Tyre. Now Assyria has joined them; Lot’s descendants strength acquire. 

3    Treat them as you treated Midian at the river Kishon drowned – Sisera and Jabin slaughtered, left like refuse on the ground. Make their chiefs like Zeeb and Oreb, Zeba and Zalmunna too, when they said, “We’ll take possession of God’s pasturelands from you.” 

