9    With help from God I can advance against a troop and rout them all, and with the aid my God will give I can leap over any wall. For perfect is the way of God; no flaw is found within his word. to all who put their trust in him a shield and refuge is the LORD. 

10    For who is God except the LORD? Besides our God, who is the Rock? He is the God who gives me strength, and he perfects the path I walk. He makes my feet like feet of deer; upon the heights he makes me stand. My arms can bend a bow of bronze; in skills of war he trains my hand. 



