1    O God, you have rejected us and torn our dwelling place. With quakes and judgments we are fed; LORD, save us now in grace. LORD, you have set your banners high to help your own to stand. That your beloved may be saved, LORD, help us by your hand. 

2    Our God speaks from his holy place:  “I will give victory. For Judah as my scepter rules; all lands will bow to me. On Edom I will cast my shoe, make Gilead my own. I use my helmet, Ephraim; they all are mine alone.” 



