1    LORD, the nations have invaded and attacked your heritage; they defiled your holy temple – crushed Jerusalem in a rage. They have given your saints’ bodies to the birds of prey as meat; and the corpses of your servants to wild animals to eat. 

2    They have poured out blood like water all around Jerusalem – bodies everywhere, and noone to give burial to them. We are objects of derision to the neighbours of our land; Scorn, reproach and degradation circle us on every hand. 



