1    I will give thanks to you, O Lord, among the people. I will sing praises to you among the nations. For your steadfast love is great, is great to the heavens, and your faithfulness, your faithfulness to the clouds. Be exalted, O God, above the heavens. Let your glory be over all the earth. Be exalted, O God, above the heavens. Let your glory be over all the earth. glory, let your glory, let your glory be over all the earth.  

2    I will lift your name on high in the presence of your people; I will praise you to the sky in adoration. For your love to me is great; greater than the mind can fathom; and your faithfulness far beyond what I can tell. Be exalted, O God, above the heavens. Let your glory be over all the earth. Be exalted, O God, above the heavens. Let your 



