1   LORD, plead my case when I am charged by foes maliciously; and fight for me when they attack and vent their spite on me. Take up your shield! Come to my aid! Speak to my soul and say, “I’m your salvation.” With your spear cut off my enemies’ way. 

2   May those who seek to take my life endure disgrace and shame; may those who plot my overthrow turn back the way they came. And may the angel of the LORD drive them away like chaff. May he pursue them all along a dark and slippery path. 

3   Since they have spread a net for me without a cause at all, and for no reason dug a pit that in it I might fall, let ruin seize them, and let them in their own net be caught; may they instead fall in their pit and so to death be brought. 

Then will my soul rejoice in God and in his saving name. “Who is a God like you, O LORD?” my heart and soul exclaim. “The poor you rescue from the hands of those who are too strong; you save the poor and weak from those who rob and do them wrong.”

Let him not gloat who, without cause, is my fierce enemy, nor those who hate me unprovoked stare spitefully at me. They do not speak in peaceful words, but cunning schemes have planned, accusing those who live at peace and quiet in the land.

O LORD, how long will you look on? Defend me from their strife; from these marauding lions’ teeth protect my precious life. Then where the great assembly meets to you I will give praise; among the crowds of worshippers in thanks my voice I’ll raise.

Malicious witnesses rise up and falsely slander me; I have no knowledge of the things they ask accusingly. They pay back evil for my good and leave my soul forlorn. Yet, at their illness, I would fast and, clad in sackcloth, mourn.

And when my prayers went out unheard, I mourned as one bereaved of mother, brother, closest friend; I bowed my head and grieved. But when I slipped they gathered round and gloated with delight; like godless jesters at a feast, they gnashed their teeth in spite.

Triumphantly they shout and say, “His wickedness we see!” LORD, you have seen; hold not your                                                 peace. LORD, be not far from me. Awake, and rise to my defence! Contend for me, my God. Do not let them gloat over me; in justice judge, O LORD.   

Let them not think within their hearts, “At last! Just what we want!” Nor let them say, “We’ve swallowed                                                 him” – let that not be their taunt. May all who gloat at my distress know shame and loss of face; may all who triumph over me be covered with disgrace.

May those who long to see me cleared shout out with joy and sing: “The LORD be praised, who loves to                                                 see his servant prospering.” I will extol your righteousness; I’ll praise you with my tongue. I will proclaim your greatness, LORD, and praise you all day long.

