1    LORD Almighty, hear my words, to my thoughts attentive be; hear my cry, my King, my God, as to you I make my plea. With the morning light O LORD, you shall hear my voice and cry; and expectant I will bring prayer as morning sacrifice. 

2    Truly you are not a God who delights in wickedness; evil shall not dwell with you, boasters not before your eyes. Lying tongues you will destroy; those who evil do, you hate. GOD abhors the man who loves violence and base deceit. 

3    Grace will lead me to your house, there to worship reverently. Make your way before me straight, lest my foes lead me astray. Not one word they say is true, ruin brews within their heart. Their mouth is an open grave, well taught in the flatterer’s art. 

