1    In doubt and temptation I rest, LORD, in thee; my hand is in thy hand, thou carest for me; My soul with thy counsel through life thou wilt guide, and afterward make me in glory abide. My God, I will extol thee and ever bless thy name; Each day will I give thanks to thee and all thy praise proclaim. 

2    In glory thou only my portion shalt be, on earth for none other I long but for thee; my flesh and heart falter but God is my stay, the strength of my spirit, my portion for aye. 



