1    In you, LORD, I take refuge; ashamed let me not be. Your righteousness eternel express by saving me; Incline your ear to hear me; with speed deliver me. To me O be a strong rock, a fort to rescue me. 

2    You are my rock and fortress; for your sake lead and guide. Free me from nets they’ve hidden; my stronghold you abide. I now commit my spirit into your outstretched hand. I know you have redeemed me, LORD God of truths that stand. 



