1    Give thanks to the Lord God and call on his name; his wonderful deeds to the nations proclaim. Sing praises to him, and his exploits record; let all those who seek him rejoice in the Lord. You chosen ones, look to the LORD and his might; seek ever his face, and his wonders recite, His miracles too, and his judgment divine you children of Abraham, Jacob’ own line. 7    Their land teemed with frogs which invaded their rooms; his word brought the gnats; swarms of flies filled their homes. The rain became hail and the lightning bolts flashed; he struck down their vines, and their fig trees were smashed. He spoke and the locusts and grasshoppers came; and every green thing was consumed as by flame. And then he took vengeance on all the firstborn – the firstfruits of manhood of Egypt were gone. 

2    The Lord is our God, and he rules all the earth. Remembering his covenant the word he set forth he vowed, for the ages to come, to make good his promise to Abr’ham, to Isaac renewed. To Jacob his sovereign decree was made sure; with Israel his covenant would always endure: "To you I will give, as your portion to stand, the country of Canaan, the beautiful land." 8    He brought Israel out bearing silver and gold; the tribes all marched forwards both steadfast and bold. Then Egypt was joyful to see them depart, for terror of them had laid hold of their heart. He spread out a cloud to protect them from sight, and fire to illumine the hours of the night. They asked, and with quails were abundantly fed; he filled them with manna, the heavenly bread. 



