1    O LORD, thou hast ascended on high in might to reign; captivity thou leadest a captive in thy train. Rich gifts to thee are offered by men who did rebel, who pray that now Jehovah their God with them may dwell. 

2    Blest be the Lord who daily our heavy burden bears, the God of our salvation, who for his people cares. Our God is near to help us, our God is strong to save; the LORD alone is able to ransom from the grave. 



