1   There was a time you told us in a vision; this to your faithful people you made known: “I have bestowed my strength upon a warrior, a young man whom I raise up to the throne. 

2   “I have sought out my faithful servant, David; I have anointed him with sacred oil. My hand will surely strengthen and sustain him; my arm will give him power for his toil. 

3   “No enemy will force him to pay tribute; no wicked one will ever bring him low. For I will crush his enemies before him; I will annihilate his every  foe. 

