1    As a deer in want of water, so I long for you, O Lord. All my heart and being falter, thirsting for your living word. When shall I behold your face? When shall I receive your grace? When shall I, your praises voicing, come before you with rejoicing? 

2    Bitter tears of lamentation are my food by night and day. In my deep humiliation “Where is now your God?” they say. When my sorrows weigh on me, then I bring to memory how with throngs I would assemble, shouting praises in your temple. 

3    O my soul, why are you grieving, why disquieted in me? Put your hope in God, believing he will still your refuge be. I again shall praise his grace for the comfort of his face; he will show his help and favour for he is my God and Saviour. 

From the land beyond the Jordan, in my grief I think of you; from the foothills of Mount Hermon I will still remember you. As the waters plunge and leap, stormy troubles o’er me sweep. Day and night God’s song is with me as a prayer to him who loves me.

Vindicate me, God, my Father, come and plead my urgent cause, for my enemies forever threaten me and flout your laws. I am safe with you alone; why do you reject your own? LORD, I need your help and blessing; keep me safe from this oppressing.   Send your light and truth to lead me: send them forth to be my guide. To your mountain let them bring me, to the place where you reside. Then, O God, I will come near and before your throne appear, to my Saviour praises bringing with the harp and joyful singing.

I will say to God, my fortress, “Why have you forgotten me? Why must I proceed in sadness, hounded by the enemy?” Their rebukes and scoffing words pierce my bones like pointed swords, as they say with proud defiance, “Where is God, your firm reliance?”  

Psalm 43

Repeat st. 3 of Psalm 42

Repeat st. 3

