1    O praise, you servants of the LORD; sing praises to his holy name. O blessed be the name of God; his praise forever more proclaim. From east to west the praise of God each day is to be spread abroad. 

2    The LORD is high above the earth, his glory far above the sky. Who else is like the LORD our God, the one who sits enthroned on high? He is the one who stoops down low to look on heaven and earth below. 



