1   How blest is he whose trespass has freely been forgiven, whose sin is wholly covered before the sight of heaven. Blest he to whom Jehovah will not impute his sin, who has a guileless spirit, whose heart is true within. 

2   While I kept guilty silence, my strength was spent with grief; thy hand was heavy on me; my soul found no relief. But when I owned my trespass, my sin hid not from thee, when I confessed transgression, then thou forgavest me. 

3   So let the godly seek thee in times when thou art near; no whelming floods shall reach them, nor cause their hearts to fear. In thee, O LORD, I hide me, thou savest me from ill, and songs of thy salvation my heart with rapture thrill. 

“I graciously will teach thee the way that thou shalt go, and with mine eye upon thee my counsel make thee know. But be ye not unruly, or slow to understand, be not perverse, but willing to heed my wise command.”

The sorrows of the wicked in number shall abound, but those that trust Jehovah, his mercy shall surround. Then in the LORD be joyful, in song lift up your voice; be glad in God, ye righteous; rejoice, ye saints, rejoice!

