1    Hallelujah, praise Jehovah, from the heavens praise his name. Praise Jehovah in the highest, all his angels, praise proclaim. All his hosts, together praise him, sun and moon and stars on high; praise him, O ye heavens of heavens, and ye floods above the sky. Let them praises give Jehovah, for his name alone is high; and his glory is exalted, and his glory is exalted, and his glory is exalted, far above the earth and sky. 

2    Let them praises give Jehovah, they were made at his command; them forever he established, his decree shall ever stand. From the earth, O praise Jehovah, all ye seas, ye monsters all, fire and hail and snow and vapours, stormy winds that hear his call. 



