1    Protect me, God: I trust in you. I say to you, “You are my Lord; on you my happiness depends.” Protect me, God: I trust in you. 

2    Your people are a chosen race, and I delight in faithful friends, but pagan ways I will not share. 

3    LORD God, you are my food and drink; my work for you is joy indeed; glad is the heritage that’s mine. 

Thank you, my LORD, for warning me; by night and day you guide my thoughts. With you before me, I stand firm. Protect me, God: I trust in you.   

Not death, but life, shall be my path; abundant joy your presence grants, an honoured place, and happiness. Protect me, God: I trust in you.    

So now I’m glad in heart and soul, for I have found security – among the dead I shall not rot. Protect me, God: I trust in you.     

