1    O my God, whose name I worship, be not silent, LORD, I pray; for the wicked and deceitful speak against me every day. They have uttered lies against me; with malicious tongues they fight. Without cause they rush upon me, closing in with words of spite. 

2    In return for love they blame me, though for them I daily pray. They reward my good with evil, for my friendship hate repay. Set an evil man against him at his right hand to denounce. May his very prayers condemn him; let the court his guilt pronounce. 



