1   My soul finds rest in God alone; from him comes my salvation sure. My safety, fortress, sheltering rock       – in him alone I am secure. 

2   How long will you assault a man? Do you all seek to lay him low     – this leaning wall, this tottering fence      – and bring about his overthrow? 

3   They plan his fall from his high place; they take delight in spreading lies. With false and flattering mouths they bless, but in their hearts curse and despise. 

My honour and salvation rest on God, my rock and mighty fort. O people, trust in him always; to him alone pour out your heart.

Find rest, my soul, in God alone; in him my hope is ever sure. My safety, fortress, sheltering rock – in him alone I am secure.

My God has spoken; I have heard that you are strong and loving, Lord. Each one according to his deeds you will assuredly reward.

Do not seek after wealth by force, or triumph in ill-gotten gain; and even though your goods increase, set not your heart on what is vain.

The lowborn man is but a breath; the highborn man is but a lie. Weighed in a balance, side by side, they come to nothing but a sigh.

