1    O LORD, my God, most earnestly my heart would seek thy face,  within thy holy house once more to see thy glorious grace.  Apart from thee I long and thirst, and nought can satisfy; I wander in a desert land where all the streams are dry. 

2    The lovingkindness of my God is more than life to me, so I will bless thee while I live and lift my prayer to thee. In thee my soul is satisfied, my darkness turns to light, and joyful meditations fill the watches of the night. 

3    My Saviour, 'neath thy sheltering wings my soul delights to dwell; still closer to thy side I press, for near thee all is well. My soul shall conquer every foe, upholden by thy hand; thy people shall rejoice in God, thy saints in glory stand. 

