1    In you, O LORD, I put my trust; shamed let me never be; O save me in your righteous ness, give ear and rescue me. O be my rock, my dwelling place, where I may always flee; for you, my rock and fortress sure, save me by your decree. 

2    Deliver me from wicked hands, save me from   men unjust, For you, Jehovah, are my hope, from youth you are my trust. You have upheld me in your grace, from child hood's  early days; to you from whom I life received will I give constant praise. 



