1    Praise the LORD! Give him glory and sing a new song. Praise the LORD with his saints in the worshipping throng. To their Maker let Israel joyfully sing; let the people of Zion be glad in their King. 

2    Let his people with dancing give praise to his name, as with harp and with timbrel their God they acclaim. For the LORD in his people takes special delight, and he crowns with salvation the meek in his sight. 



