1    In all the earth, O LORD our Lord, how glorious is your name! For you have set above the heavens your glory and your fame. From infants' and from children's lips you ordered praise to sound, to silence all your enemies, the wicked to confound. All flocks and herds, all birds and fish, all beasts both wild and tame. In all the earth, O LORD our Lord, how glorious is your name! 

2    When I regard the heavens you made, your fingers' work I trace; I see the moon and shining stars which you have set in place. I ask myself, “What then is man that you should give him thought; the son of man, that you to him such gracious care have brought?” 



