The LORD answer you when you cry in distress; may Jacob’s God keep you, whose name you confess. May God send assistance from his holy place, and grant you from Zion support by his grace. 

May God keep in mind every sacrifice made; accept on the altar your offerings laid. And may he fulfil the desire of your heart – success to each one of your plans to impart. 

With joy we will shout when your victory’s won; we’ll lift up our banners in God’s name alone. And so may the LORD hear your earnest request, and answer your prayers as it seems to him best. 

Now truly I know that the LORD from above protects his anointed in covenant love; from heav’n in his holiness GOD hears his cry, and saves by the pow’r of his right hand on high.   In horses or chariots some trust for defence, but in our LORD’s name is our strong confidence. They’re brought to their knees, while in strength we arise. O LORD, save the king!  Hear and answer our cries!

