1    Hallelujah, praise Jehovah, O my soul, Jehovah praise; I will sing the glorious praises of my God through all my days. Put no confidence in princes, nor for help on man depend; he shall die, to dust returning, and his purposes shall end. 

2    Happy is the man that chooses Israel's God to be his aid; he is blest whose  hope of blessing on the LORD his God is stayed. Heaven and earth the LORD created, seas and all that they contain; he delivers from oppression, righteousness he will maintain. 



