1    I love you, LORD! You are my strength. A fortress is the   LORD to me – my rock and my deliverer; for refuge to my God I flee. He is my stronghold and my shield, the LORD  who saves me by his might. I'll call on him and give him  praise. I'm saved; he puts  my foes to flight. 

2    The  cords of death entangled me; destruction hit me like a wave. Encircled by the snares of death, I faced the terrors of the grave. In my distress I called on God; I cried out to the LORD  for aid. He from his temple heard my voice; he listened to the prayer I made. 



