1    Shout to the LORD with joy, all who to earth belong. Adore the LORD with joyful hearts and come to him in song. Know that the LORD is God; he made us as his own. We are the sheep for whom he cares – his people, his alone. 

2    Enter his gates with praise, his courts with thankfulness. Your praises gladly sing to him; his name forever bless. For God the LORD is good; his love is ever sure. His constant truth and faithfulness through every age endure. 



