1    Praise God,   my soul! With all my heart let me exalt his holy name. Forget not all his benefits; his praise, my soul, in song proclaim. The Lord forgives you all your sins, and heals your sickness and distress; your life he rescues from the grave. And crowns you in his tenderness. 

2    He satisfies your deep desires from his unending stores of good, so that, just like the eagle’s strength, your youthful vigour is renewed. The Lord is known for righteous acts and justice to downtrodden ones. To Moses he made known his ways. His mighty deeds to Israel's sons. 



