1    Hail to the LORD's anointed, great David's greater son! Hail, in the time appointed, his reign on earth begun! He comes to break oppression, to set the captive free, to take away transgression, and rule in equity. 

2    He shall come down like showers upon the fruitful earth; and love, joy, hope, like flowers, spring in his path to birth. The king shall have dominion from sea to shining sea, and over every nation his peaceful rule shall be. 



