1    The fool speaks in his heart; “There is no God,” he says. They are corrupt, their deeds are vile; none walk in godly ways. The LORD looks down from heaven upon the human race, to see if any understand, if any seek God’s face. 

2    They have all turned aside; corrupt they have become. Not one of them does any good – no, not a single one. Will sinners never learn? My people they’ve devoured as if they were consuming bread; they never seek the LORD. 

3    Struck down they are with dread, for God is with the just. You evildoers shame the poor, but in the LORD they trust. 

