1    God is known among his people, every mouth his praises fill; from of old he has established his abode on Zion's hill; there he broke the sword and arrow, bade the noise of war be still. 

2    Excellent and glorious art thou, with thy trophies from the fray; thou hast slain the valianthearted, wrapt in sleep of death are they; when thine anger once is risen, who can stand in that dread day? 



