1    The LORD unto my Lord has said, “Sit here at my right hand until I make your enemies submit to your command.” A scepter prospered by the LORD your mighty hand shall wield; from Zion you shall rule the world, and all your foes shall yield. 

2    Your people will be gladly yours when you arise in might. like dawning day, like hopeful youth, with holy beauty bright. The priesthood of Melchizedek the LORD has given you; it shall remain forevermore; God's word is always true. 



