1    On the holy mountain the Lord laid his foundation. He loves the gates of Zion far above all the dwelling places in all of Jacob's nation. Glorious praise is yours O city of the Lord. Tyre and Ethiopia and also Babylon, Rahab and Philistia in Zion born. In Zion born! 

2    Zion, blessed Zion, by God most high established, they say this one and that in her were born. There will be salvation for every tribe and nation, for the Lord shall count them all his very own. Flutes and instruments will lead the throng and they will sing, “All my founts of joyful praise from Zion spring. From Zion spring!” 



