1    O  God, be merciful, be merciful to me, for man, with constant hate, would love to trample me. My many enemies against me proudly fight; to overwhelm my soul they watch from morn to    night. 

2    Whenever I’m afraid, I put my trust in you. In God I rest; and praise his word so rich and true. In God I put my trust; I neither doubt nor fear; what can man do to me with God my helper near? 

3    All day they twist my words; their thoughts are full of hate. They meet, they lurk, they watch, as for my soul they wait. Shall they by wickedness escape your judgment right? O God of righteousness, destroy them in your might. 

