1    The spacious heavens declare the glory of our God; the wide expanse displays his handiwork abroad; from day to day they utter speech, and night to night they knowledge teach. 

2    Aloud they do not speak; they utter forth no word, nor into language break; their voice is never heard, yet through the world their truth extends, their words to earth’s remotest ends. 

3    In heaven God pitched a tent, a dwelling for the sun, which like a bridegroom comes, or strong man keen to run. Its course from east to west complete – there’s nothing hidden from its heat. 

Jehovah’s perfect law restores the soul again; his testimony sure makes wise the simple one; the precepts of the LORD are right and fill the heart with great delight.   The LORD’s commands are clear, light to the eyes restore; the fear of GOD is pure, enduring evermore; his judgments, let the world confess, are wholly truth and righteousness.   

They’re more to be desired than stores of finest gold; than honey from the comb more sweetness far they hold. With warnings they your servant guard,  in keeping them is great reward.   His errors who can know? Forgive my hidden sin; keep me from wilful sins, nor let them o’er me reign; and blameless then I shall appear, and be from great transgressions clear.   

Let all the words I speak  and all the thoughts within come up before your sight and your approval win, O LORD, you are a rock to me; you have redeemed and set me free. 

