1   O LORD, I will exalt your name for you have rescued me; you did not let my foes rejoice and gloat triumphantly. LORD God, in need I cried to you and you restored my health. O LORD, you brought me from the grave and saved my soul from death. 

2   You holy ones, sing to the LORD; sing out with joyful voice. When you recall his holy name, then praise him and rejoice. His anger but a moment lasts; lifelong his favour stays. Though tears may last throughout the night, joy comes with morning’s rays. 

3   “I never shall be moved,” I said in my prosperity. You made my mountain firm and strong when you, LORD, favoured me. But when you hid your face from me my heart was terrified. To you, O LORD, I called aloud; for mercy, Lord, I cried. 

What gain will my destruction bring if I descend to death? Will dust proclaim your faithfulness or praise you with its breath? Hear as I cry, O LORD my God, and listen to my plea. Come to my aid in my distress; have mercy, LORD, on me.  

You turned my wailing into dance; no longer was I sad. My sackcloth gone, you gave me clothes of joy, and I was glad. Therefore my heart will sing to you and never cease to praise; to your great name, O LORD my God, I will give thanks always.

