1    My God, my God, O why have you in my distress forsaken me? O why so far from giving help and from my agonizing plea? All day, my God, I cry in vain; by night, but no relief I gain. 

2    But still you are the holy one; in Israel's praise you are enthroned. Our fathers put their trust in you; they trusted, found their prayer was owned; to you they cried; deliverance came; they trusted and they knew no shame. 



