Protect me, O my God; you are my refuge true. I said, “You are my Lord: I have no good apart from you.” The godly in the land, for holiness renowned – they are the glorious ones, in whom all my delight is found. 

Their sorrows will increase who on false gods rely. I will not sacrifice to them; their worship I defy. O LORD, you are to me my cup and portion sure; the share that is assigned to me you guard and keep secure. 

The land allotted me is in a pleasant site; and surely my inheritance to me is a delight. I’ll praise the LORD my God, whose counsel guides my choice; and even in the night, my heart recalls instruction’s voice. 

