1    Endow the king with justice, LORD, the royal son with righteousness. Your people, your afflicted ones, he'll judge with truth and uprightness. The moun tains will bring peace to them, the hills the fruit of righteousness. He will defend and save the poor, and crush all those who them oppress. 

2    As long as sun and moon endure, so will he live time without end. He'll be like showers on the earth, like rains that on mown fields descend. The righteous then will blossom forth through out his everlasting reign. Until the moon no longer shines, peace in abundance will remain. 



