1   In times past, LORD, you showed favour to your own beloved land; the prosperity of Jacob you restored by your strong hand. You forgave your people's trespass; you were pleased their sins to hide. You withdrew all your displeasure; from your wrath you turned aside. 

2   God our Saviour, now restore us; from us turn away your rage. Will your anger burn against us? Will it last from age to age? Will you not again revive us, that we may rejoice in you? Show us, LORD, your covenant mercy; your salvation grant anew 

3   I will hear what God the LORD says: to his saints he offers peace; but his people must not wander and return to foolishness. Surely for all those who fear him his salvation is at hand, so that once again his glory may be seen within our land 

