1    O thank the LORD, for he is good; his love endures always. Let those whom God redeemed say this, those rescued by his grace. He saved them from their enemies and brought them from the lands, from east and west, from north and south, safe from oppressing hands. 1    O thank the LORD, for he is good, his love endures always. Let those whom God redeemed say this, those rescued by his grace. He saved them from their enemies and brought them from the lands, from east and west, from north and south, safe from oppressing hands. 

2    Some wandered in the desert wastes, not finding any way to reach a city where they might obtain a place to stay. Their life and strength were ebbing fast in thirst and emptiness. Then in despair they sought the LORD, who saved them from distress. 2    Some wandered in the desert wastes, not finding any way to reach a city where they might obtain a place to stay. Their life and strength were ebbing fast in thirst and emptiness. Then in despair they sought the LORD, who saved them from distress. 



