1    LORD, you are the God who saves me; I entreat you night and day. May my pleading come before you; turn your ear to me, I pray. 

2    For my soul is full of trouble and my life draws near to death. Counted with the ones who perish, I have neither strength nor breath. 

3    To the grave I am abandoned, like the bodies lying there. You remember them no longer; they are cut off from your care. 

