1    How good it is to thank the LORD, to praise your name with tuneful chord, to show your love with morning light and tell your faithfulness each night. Yes, it is good your praise to sing, and all our sweetest music bring. 

2    O LORD, my song with joy expands before the wonders of your hands. How great the works that you have wrought; how deep, O LORD, your every thought! A foolish man knows not their worth, nor he whose mind is of the earth. 

3    Though as the grass the wicked grow, those evildoers do not know the endless ruin they will see. But God will reign eternally. All foes will fall before his might; the wicked shall be put to flight. 

