1    Sing a new song to Jehovah for the won  ders he has wrought. His right hand and arm most holy triumph to his cause have brought. In his love and tender mercy he has made salvation known, In the sight of every nation, he his righteous ness has shown. 

2    Truth and mercy toward his people he has ever kept in mind, and his full and free salvation he has  shown to all mankind. Sing, O earth,  sing to Jehovah, praises to Jehovah sing; with the swelling notes of music shout before the LORD, the King. 



