1    The heavens declare thy glory, the firmament thy power; day unto day the story repeats from hour to hour; night unto night replying, proclaims in every land, O Lord, with voice undying, the wonders of thy hand. 

2    The sun with royal splendour goes forth to chant thy praise, and moonbeams soft and tender their gentler anthem raise; o’er every tribe and nation the music strange is poured, the song of all creation to thee, creation’s Lord. 

3    All heaven on high rejoices to do its Maker’s will; the stars with solemn voices resound thy praises still; so let my whole behaviour, thoughts, words and actions be, O LORD, my strength, my Saviour, one ceaseless song to thee. 

