1    O Lord of hosts, how lovely thy tabernacles are; for them my heart is yearning in banishment afar. My soul is longing, fainting, thy sacred courts to see; my heart and flesh are crying, O living God for thee. 

2    Beneath thy care the sparrow finds place for peaceful rest; to keep her young in safety the swallow finds a nest; then, Lord, my king almighty, thy love will shelter me; beside thy holy altar my dwellingplace shall be. 

3    Blest they who dwell in Zion, whose joy and strength thou art; forever they will praise thee, thy ways are in their heart. Though tried, their tears like showers shall fill the springs of peace, and all the way to Zion their strength shall still increase. 

