1   LORD, speak for me, for I am yours; and test my mind and heart. I walk with steady trust in you, nor from your ways depart. 

2   Try me, O LORD, if I be true and walk in righteousness. Your love forever leads my way; I trust your faithfulness. 

3    I do not sit with those who cheat – the false who love pretence. I do not follow where they go, nor count them as my friends. 

I wash my hands in innocence and seek your altar, LORD, and, singing there with thankful voice, your mighty works record.

I love your house, O mighty LORD, I love the holy place where you in your great glory dwell; you visit us in grace.

O do not sweep me down to death with those who thirst for blood; their right hands overflow with bribes; they turn away from good.

I walk in my integrity; redeem me, LORD, in grace. Securely now I stand, O LORD; in worship I bring praise.

