1    I said, “Now let me watch my ways and keep my tongue from sin. I'll put a muzzle on my mouth when I'm with wicked men.” When I was silent and kept still and firmly held my peace, not speaking even what was good, this made my pain increase. 

2    Because of this my heart grew hot; the fire burned strong indeed the more I mused upon it all. Then I began to plead: “LORD, show me that my life will end – how many days I'll see – and cause me, LORD, to understand, how brief my life will be. 



