1    There where the judges gather, a greater takes his seat; “How long,” he asks the judges, “will you pronounce deceit? How long show special favour to those of ill repute? How long neglect the orphaned, the poor and destitute? 

2    “Deal justly with the needy, protect the fatherless, deliver the afflicted from those who would oppress. But you are wholly blinded, you do not understand; therefore foundations totter, injustice rocks the land.” 

3    God speaks: “I named you rulers, sons of the Most High God; but you shall die as mortals and perish by my rod.” Arise, O God, in judgment, your sovereignty make known; for yours are all the nations, the peoples are your own. 

