1    Not unto us, O LORD of heaven, but unto you be glory given; in love and truth you do fulfil the counsels of your sovereign will. Though nations fail your power to own, you are the King – you reign alone. 

2    The idol gods of heathen lands are but the work of human hands: they cannot see, they cannot speak, their ears are deaf, their hands are weak. Like them shall be all those who hold to gods of silver  and of gold. 



