1    O God, to us show mercy and bless us in your grace, and cause to shine upon us the brightness of your face, so that your way most holy on earth may soon be known, and unto every people your saving grace be shown. 

2    Let all the peoples praise you, let all the nations sing; in every land let praises and songs of gladness ring; for you will judge the peoples in truth and righteousness, and on the earth all nations will your just rule confess. 



