1    Hear, O LORD, and answer me; I am poor, and needy too. Guard my life; save me my God, for your servant trusts in you. Lord, be merciful to me; all day long to you I call. Give your servant joy, O LORD, for to you I lift my soul. 

2    You, O Lord, alone are good; you are ready to forgive. To all those who call on you, you abound in steadfast love. Hear my earnest prayer, O LORD; listen to my troubled cry. In distress I'll call on you, for in mercy you'll reply. 

3    Lord, among the many gods there is none to rival you; deeds that others may perform never match what you can do. Lord, the nations you have made will come near and praise your name. You alone are God; your deeds bring to you outstanding fame. 

