1    Praise the LORD! Extol his goodness! for his love endures always. Who can tell his mighty actions, or in full declare his praise? Blessed are those whose way is right, actat ing  the justly in his sight. 

2    When you show your people favour, then, O LORD, remember me. Help me when you come to save them; let me know prosperity – joyful with your chosen race, joining them in giving praise. 



