1    Hear, O Israel's shepherd, hear us; Joseph like a flock you lead. You who are enthroned in glory, shine upon us in our need. 

2    Shine on Benjamin, Manasseh and for Ephraim rouse your might! Turn us once again toward you; come and save us, give us light! 

3    O LORD God, the Lord Almighty, all our prayers you do not hear. How long will your anger smoulder and our enemies still jeer? 

