 1    Praise is your   right, O God, in Zion. To you we pay our vows. When we your people pray, you hear us. All flesh to you will bow. When our transgressions overwhelm us, you graciously forgive. How satisfied your chosen servants; within your courts they live. 

2    Your mighty acts work our salvation. All earth  waits hopefully. You have the strength to make the mountains, to calm the stormy sea. You calm the tumult of the people. Such awesome signs you do that earth, from sunrise to the sunset, for joy cries out to you. 



