1    On the good and faithful God has set his love; when they call he sends them blessings from above. Stand in awe and sin not, bid your heart be still; through the silent watches, think upon his will. 

2    Lay upon God's altar good and loving deeds, and in all things trust him to supply your needs. Anxious and despairing, many walk in night; but to those that fear him, God will send his light. 



