1   Do not fret on account of the wicked, do not envy the ones who do wrong; for like grass they will very soon wither, like green plants they will not flourish long. 13    If 12    The the unLORD godtakes ly derelight tain in what a they perborson, row, he but will the renjust der give his with steps genfirm erand ous sure. hand. For Though  those he stumblest ble by he the will LORD not will fall inheadherlong, it, for while the the LORD's cursed hand are will cut keep off him from sethe cure. land. 

2   Put your trust in the LORD and be upright; then secure in the land you will live. Take delight in the LORD above all things – the desires of your heart he will give. 14    All my life I have not seen the righteous left forsaken, or begging for food. They are always prepared to lend freely, and their children will share what is good. 

3   To the LORD let your way be committed; trust in him     – he will do what is right. Then your justice will shine like the morning, your just cause like the sun in its might. 

So be silent and seek the LORD’s presence, and be patient until he replies; do not fret when you see the successful, if their schemes are promoted through lies.

If you turn back from sin and act rightly, you'll continue forever secure; for the LORD shows his love to the righteous; those who trust him he'll keep safe and sure.   The obedient will not be forsaken,  but the line of the wicked will fail.  To the righteous the land will be given,  and forever in it they will dwell.   From the mouth of the righteous comes wisdom; words of justice proceed from their lips. For the law of their God is within them and ensures that their foot never slips.   The unjust lie in wait for the righteous; to destroy them is always their thought. But the LORD will not let them be mastered, or condemned when to court they are brought.   Put your trust in the LORD, I exhort you; in his ways you should always remain. To inherit the land he’ll exalt you; you will see when the wicked are slain.   I have witnessed a ruthless man standing like a flourishing tree in its ground; but he soon passed away and was nothing; though I searched, he was not to be found.   Watch the blameless, consider the upright; there’s a future for those who make peace. But destruction awaits the rebellious, and their future will suddenly cease.   From the LORD comes the hope of the righteous, and in trouble defence for the meek; so the LORD saves them all from the wicked, for in him their protection they seek.

Though the wicked may strike at the righteous, and may gnash their teeth wildly in hate; yet the LORD simply laughs at the wicked, for he sees the approach of their fate.

Do not fret – it leads only to evil; keep your temper and stay far from wrath, for the wicked will certainly perish, while the godly inherit the earth.

Yet a while, and the wicked will vanish; though you search, they will never be found. But the land will belong to the humble, and their welfare and peace will abound.

Though the wicked take aim at the righteous and attempt to bring down the oppressed, yet their bow will be broken in pieces, and their sword will but pierce their own breast.

Though the righteous have little, it’s better than the riches of many unjust; for the wicked’s great strength will be broken, but the LORD is the righteous one’s trust.

Day by day the LORD cares for the blameless, so their heritage stands ever sure. When a famine comes, they will have plenty; and in drought they will always endure.

But the wicked will certainly perish; they will vanish, as smoke blows away. And the foes of the LORD will be scattered, like the flower of the field in a day.

