1   O my people, hear my teaching; parables I will unfold. Give attention as I utter dark and hidden things of old – things that we have heard and known; by our fathers they were shown. 

2   We will tell them to our children, generations yet to come; we will show the LORD’s great power and the wonders he has done. Laws for Israel he made, statutes firm to be obeyed. 

3   These he ordered our forefathers to their families to tell, so the coming generation, not yet born, would know them well, and their children, in their turn, God’s commands and laws would learn. 

Then to God they would be faithful, mindful of what he had done – not like their disloyal fathers, stubborn rebels every one; for God’s word they had denied and his precepts they defied.  Such were those of Ephraim’s army who, though strong and armed with bows, to the cov’nant were disloyal, turned their back upon their foes. They forgot what God had done and the wonders he had shown.

