1    Sing to the LORD, sing his praise, all you peoples; new be your song as new honours you pay. Sing of his majesty, praise him forever, show his salvation from day to day. 

2    Tell of his wondrous works, tell of his glory, till through the nations his name is revered. Praise and exalt him, for he is almighty; God over all, let the LORD be feared. 

3    Vain are the idols and gods of the nations; God made the heavens, and his glory they tell. Splendour and majesty shine out before him; glory and strength in his temple dwell. 

