1    How blest the man who does not walk where wicked men would guide his feet, nor stand in paths with sinful men, nor sit upon the scorner's seat. The LORD's own law is his delight, his meditation day and night. 

2    He shall be like a growing tree, well planted by the water side, which in its season bears its fruit, and has a leaf which does not fade. In all to which he puts his mind prosperity he'll surely find. 

3    Not so the wicked! They are all like chaff the wind will drive away. They shall not in the judgement stand, nor sinners with the righteous stay. The LORD the way of just men knows; the sinners' way he overthrows. 

