1   Jehovah is my light and my salvation near; who shall my soul affright or cause my heart to fear? while GOD my strength, my life sustains, secure from fear my soul remains. 

2   When evildoers came to make my life their prey, they stumbled in their shame and fell in sore dismay; though hosts make war on every side, still fearless I in GOD confide. 

3   My one request has been, and still this prayer I raise, that I may dwell within GOD’s house through all my days, Jehovah’s beauty to admire, and in his temple to inquire. 

