1    Blest is the one who cares for those in need; the LORD delivers him in times of strife. The LORD will surely bless him in the land; he will protect him and preserve his life. 

2    He will not hand him over to his foes that they may satisfy their evil will. The LORD will on his sickbed give him help, and he will raise him up when he is ill. 

3    I said, “Be merciful to me, O LORD; heal me, because against you I have sinned.” My enemies with malice say of me, “When will he die – his name come to an end?” 

They visit me with falsehood in their hearts and then go out and spread their wicked lies. Against me all my foes are whispering; the worst of fates for me their minds devise.   They say, “A vile disease has struck him down; he never will get up and leave his bed.” My closest friend has turned his back on me – my trusted friend, with whom I shared my bread.  

   But you, O LORD, be merciful to me and raise me up their malice to repay. I know that you are pleased with me, O LORD; for over me my foe does not hold sway.   In my integrity you hold me fast; before you I will constantly remain. O praise the LORD, the God of Israel, forever and forevermore! Amen. 

