1    All those who trust the LORD like Zion are secure which never can be moved but always will endure. Just as the mountains stand around Jerusalem, the LORD surrounds his own, forever guarding them. 



3    But God will banish those who choose a crooked way; they'll share the sinner's fate, let peace on Israel stay. All those who trust the LORD like Zion are secure which never can be moved but always will endure. 

