1  I said, “Now let me watch my ways and keep my tongue from sin. I’ll put a muzzle on my mouth while I’m with wicked men.” When I was silent and kept still and firmly held my peace, not speaking even what was good, this made my pain increase.  

2  Be- cause of this my heart grew hot; the fire burned strong indeed the more I mused upon it all. Then I began to plead: “LORD, show me that my life will end, how many days I’ll see— and cause me, LORD, to understand how briefmy life will be.  

3  “O Lord, how short you make my days before I sink in death. My years are nothing in your sight; man’s life is but a breath. Like shadows people go about; they bustle to and fro. They heap up wealth, but do not know to whomtheir wealth will go.  

“But now, what do I look for, LORD?    My hope is set on you. From my transgressions rescue me    lest fools in scorn pursue. I held my peace and would not speak,    for you did this, I know. Remove your scourge from me; your hand    has struck and laid me low.

“For as your guest I stay a while.    I’m like my fathers all— a stranger and a pilgrim here.    Have mercy when I call. O turn away your eyes from me.    Let me rejoice again before I finally depart    and here no more remain.”

“For you rebuke and punish men    for their iniquity. You, like a moth, consume their wealth;    each man is vanity. O LORD, please listen to my prayer    and hear my cry for aid; Do not be deaf to the appeal    which I with tears have made.

