1   Make haste, O God, to save me; O LORD, come to my aid. May those who seek to kill me be utterly dismayed. May all who seek my ruin be turned back in disgrace, and may all those who mock me with shame their steps retrace. 

2   But may all those who seek you rejoice in you always; may those who love salvation say, “To our God be praise!” Yet I am poor and needy; come quickly, God, I pray. You are my help and Saviour; O LORD, do not delay. 



