Help, LORD, for godly men are few; the faithful vanish from mankind. Men to their neighbours falsely speak; smooth speech and double talk are theirs. O may the LORD cut off such lips, the tongue that speaks so boastfully! 

They’ve said, “Our tongue can win the day; words are our strength – who is our lord?” But says the LORD, “Now I will arise, and for the plundered poor will act, and for the needy who lament, I’ll grant the safety which they crave.” 

The sayings of the LORD are pure, like silver smelted seven times. You, LORD, indeed will keep us safe, you’ll ever guard us from this race. The wicked freely strut about when vileness is esteemed by men. 

