O LORD, how are my foes increased! Against me many rise! And many speak of me and say: “His God no help supplies.” 

But you’re my shield and glory, LORD! You lift my head up high! And from his holy hill the LORD gives answer to my cry. 

I lay down, slept, and woke again: the LORD sustains my life. I will not fear the many foes who plot to cause me strife. 

Arise, O LORD! Save me, my God! You’ve always struck my foes: the jaw and teeth of wicked men are broken by your blows.   Salvation and deliverance come from the LORD alone. O let the blessing of your grace be to your people shown.

