1   O hear my cry, my righteous God. Relieve me; I’m distressed. Display your mercy to me now, and answer my request. 

2   The glory of my name, O men, how long will you despise? How long will you delude yourselves, still searching after lies? 

3   Know that the LORD has set apart the godly as his own; the LORD will hear me when I call and my request make known. 

Though you are angry, do not sin. O search your heart; be still. Present a righteous sacrifice; trust in the LORD’s good will.   “O who can show us any good?” I hear so many say. O LORD, shine on us with your light; show us your face, I pray.   You filled my heart with greater joy than others may have found as they rejoiced at harvest time, when grain and wine abound.   I will lie down and sleep in peace; my heart will rest secure, for you alone, O gracious LORD, will keep me safe and sure.

