1   The LORD my Shepherd holds me within his tender care, and with his flock he folds me, no want shall find me there. In pastures green he feeds me, with plenty I am blessed; by quiet streams he leads me and makes me safely rest. 

2   Whatever ill betides me, he will restore and bless; for his name’s sake he guides me in paths of righteousness. Your rod and staff shall cheer me in death’s dark vale and shade, for you will then be near me; I shall not be afraid. 

3   My food you do appoint me, supplied before my foes; with oil you do anoint me, my cup of bliss o’erflows. Your goodness, LORD, shall guide me, your mercy cheer my way; a home you will provide me within your house for aye. 

