The LORD is my refuge, how then can you say, “O flee like a bird to your mountain away. The godless, they target with bow and with dart, like snipers they shoot at the upright in heart. 

“When such is the case, they foundations destroy; what strategy, then, can the righteous employ?” Be sure that the LORD in his temple on high, in heaven enthroned, over men casts his eye. 

The LORD sees us all, and his eyes test each one, both righteous and godless in all they have done. His soul hates all those who wild violence pursue: the wicked will doubtlessly get their own due. 

