1  My light and my salvation, O LORD, whom shall I fear? You are my life’s great stronghold when evil men come near. Though enemies attack me, my heart will never fear. Though war break out against me, I’m confident you’re near. 

2  One thing I ask and seek, LORD: to dwell with you always, to gaze upon your beauty and seek you all my days. For in the day of trouble, you’ll hide me, keep me safe. My head will be exalted; I’ll sing and shout your praise. 

3  Hear now my voice and answer; be merciful I pray. Your face, LORD, I seek daily; do not turn me away. For you have been my helper; do not reject me, God. Though family may forsake me, I know that you will not. 

Teach me your way, my Saviour; in straight paths may I walk. Don’t let my foes oppress me with false and vicious talk. Of this I still am certain: I’ll see GOD’s goodness yet. Wait for the LORD Jehovah; be strong, take heart, and wait.

