1   O hear my urgent cry, my God, and listen to my plea. From earth’s remotest bounds I call when my heart faints in me. 

2   O God, conduct me to the rock that’s higher far than I. For you’re my refuge from the foe, my tower of strength on high. 

3   O let me dwell within your tent, forever there to live! O for the shelter of your wings, the refuge which they give! 

For you have heard my vows, O God, and you have given me the heritage of those who fear your name continually.

Prolong the days the king will live; his sovereign rule extend for many generations more, established without end.

May he forever sit as king enthroned before God’s face; appoint your love and faithfulness as his protecting grace.

Then will I ever bless your name with songs of joy and praise, and will fulfil my holy vows with care throughout my days.

