1    O God, we have heard and our fathers have told what wonders you did in the great days of old. The nations were crushed and expelled by your hand; you planted our fathers to dwell in the land. 

2    They gained not the land by the edge of their sword; their own arm to them could no safety afford, ’twas your arm, your right hand, the light of your face, for you showed them favour, your wonderful grace. 

3    O God, you alone are forever my King; command and for Jacob deliverance bring. Through you we will surely put down all our foes; through your name we'll trample on all who oppose. 

But now you forsake us, to shame bring our boasts; no more into battle accomp’ny our hosts. You make us turn back from our foe in dismay, and these our opponents have made us their prey.  You give us like sheep to be slaughtered for food, among all the nations dispersed and pursued. You sell off your people to strangers for nought; their price to your treas’ry no increase has brought.  You make all our neighbours reproach us in pride, and cause those around us to scoff and deride. The nations revile us and joke at our name; they taunt and they threaten: I always know shame.  This happened though we had been faithful to you;   we always have been to your covenant true. Our heart has not turned back, our steps have not strayed, though made like a ruin and under death’s shade.  If we had forgotten the name of our God, or worshipped an idol, would God then not know? for he knows the secrets in everyone’s heart; so why do we face death all day for your sake?  We’re thought to be destined for slaughter like sheep. Awake, O Defender! for why do you sleep? Rise up! Don’t forget us forever, we plead. O why hide your face from our sorrow and need?  Our lives are all broken, we’re brought very low; our bodies lie crushed on the ground in our woe. Rise up! Be our helper! Redeem from the dust, because in your covenant mercy we trust.

No trust will I place in my sword or my bow, for you are my Saviour from hater and foe. In God we will boast, for you put them to shame, all day and forever we’ll praise your great name. 

