1    Jehovah sits enthroned in majesty most bright, appareled in omnipotence, and girded round with might. 

2    The world established stands on its foundations broad; his throne is fixed, he reigns supreme, the everlasting God. 

3    The floods have lifted up their voice in majesty, but mighty is the Lord our God above the raging sea. 

Thy testimonies, Lord,    in faithfulness excel, And holy must thy servants be    who in thy temple dwell.

