1    My soul, bless the Lord! the Lord is most great, With glory arrayed, majestic His state; The light is His garment, the skies are his shade, And over the waters His courts He has laid. 

2    He rides on the clouds, the wings of the storm, The lightning and wind His mission perform; The earthy He has founded her station to keep, And wrapped as a vesture about her the deep. 

3    O’er mountain and plain the dark waters raged; His voice they obeyed, the floods were assuaged; Uplifting the mountains He ordered a bound, Forbidding the waters to cover the ground. 

