1    The mighty God and sovereign  LORD has called the earth from sea to sea. From Zion’s beauty God shines forth; he comes and will not silent be. Devouring flame before him goes, and dark the tempest round him grows. 

2    God summons earth and heaven above to witness how he tries his own: “Now gather all my chosen saints, who covenant with me alone.” His righteousness the heavens declare, for God himself is judging there. 

3    “Hear, O my people, I will speak; against you I will testify. Give ear to me, O Israel, for God, your faithful God, am I. I do not spurn your sacrifice; your offerings are before my eyes. 

“I do not need a goat or bull as offering for my holy shrine. The cattle on a thousand hills and all the forest beasts are mine. Each mountain bird to me is known; whatever roams the field I own.   “If I were hungry, who would know? I would not look to you for food. The world and all it has is mine; I have no need of flesh or blood. But pay your vows and call on me; then I will set my people free.”

“Consider my rebuke and charge, all you who have forgotten me, or I will tear you all apart – then what deliverance will you see? But those who sacrifice with praise will always know my boundless grace.”

But to the wicked, God declares: “What right have you to quote my law? Why take my covenant on your lips when evil you will not withdraw? My holy words you make profane; you cast them from you in disdain.   “You are a scheming friend of thieves, of those who break their marriage vows. Your tongues speak evil and deceit; you slander those within your house. You thought that I was just like you, that there was nothing I would do!

