 13    Thy Spirit O Lord, makes life to abound, The earth is renewed, and fruitful the ground; To God ascribe glory and wisdom and might, Let God in His Creatures forever delight. 

 14    Before the Lord's might earth trembles and quakes, The mountains are rent, and smoke from them breaks; The Lord I will worship through all of my days, Yea, while I have being my God I will praise. 

15    Rejoicing in God, mu thought shall be sweet, While sinners depart in ruin complete; My soul, bless Jehovah, His NAme be adored, Come, praise Him, ye People, and worship the Lord. 

