1   Joyfully sing to the LORD, all you righteous; for it is good that the upright give praise. With harp and lyre praise the LORD and make music; with shouts of joy, a new song to him raise. 

2   Righteous and true is the word God has spoken; all the LORD’s actions his faithfulness prove. He loves true righteousness, judgment and justice; all earth is full of his unfailing love. 

3   By the LORD’s word were the heavens created, their starry host by the breath from his lips. All the sea’s waters he gath ers together and in his storehouses lays up the deeps. 

