1    Lord, you have been our dwelling place through all the ages of our race. Before you gave the mountains birth or formed and fashioned all the earth, from years which no beginning had to years unending, you are God! 

2    You turn man back to dust again; you say, “Return to dust, O men!” For in your sight a thousand years like yesterday, when past, appears; a thousand years are in your sight brief as a portion of the night. 

3    You with a flood have swept men on, so like a sleep they're quickly gone. They're like the grass which quickly grows— each morning its new growth it shows; though green beneath the morning sun, it's withered ere the day is done. 

For by your anger we’re consumed, and by your wrath to terror doomed. Our sins you set before your sight, our secret sins in your clear light. Beneath your wrath we fade and die; our years are finished with a sigh.

For some life’s years are seventy; perhaps the strong may eighty see. Yet is their best but toil and woe; all quickly ends; how soon we go! Who has your anger understood? Who fears your fury as he should?

Teach us to count aright our days, to set our hearts in wisdom’s ways. Return, O LORD! How long will it be? Let us, your servants, mercy see. Your grace send with the morning rays; we’ll sing for joy through all our days.  Give joy that answers all the tears, the troubles in those days and years. Your work to all your children show; your glory on their sons bestow. O Lord our God, let favour rest; our works confirm, our labours bless.

