1    Mighty mortal, boasting evil, why plot mischief every day? Your sharp tongue is like a razor, cutting with each word you say. You love evil more than goodness, harmful words that will devour, lying more than speaking truly, O you tongue of awful power! 

2    God will bring you down to ruin; from your place you will be sent. In the sight of righteous people God will pluck you from your tent. Then the righteous, filled with laughter, will cry out, “Behold this fool! He would not make God his refuge; money was his golden rule.” 

3    In the house of God I flourish like a growing olive tree. Trusting in God’s love forever, I will praise him thankfully. For I know that you have done this; I will hope in your good name. In the presence of your people I your goodness will proclaim. 

