1   Sing for joy to God our Saviour; shout aloud to Jacob's Lord! Start the music; strike the timbrel; play on strings a pleasing chord. Sound the trumpet at the New Moon and at the full moon as well, at the feast by God appointed and decreed for Israel. 

2   God ordained this law for Joseph when he ravaged Egypt's land; there we listened to a language which we did not understand. He said: "I removed their burdens and their aching hands set free. I delivered you from trouble when you called for help to me. 

3   "From the thundercloud of Sinai all your people I addressed; when at Meribah you murmured, there I put you to the test. Hear, my people, let me warn you— if you would but listen now! No strange god shall be among you; to a false god do not bow. 

“I, who brought you up from Egypt,    your own God, the LORD, am I; open wide your mouth towards me,    and your food I will supply. But my people would not listen—    would not do what I required. So I gave them up to follow    what their stubborn hearts desired. 

“If my people would but heed me,    Isr’el follow my command, I would soon subdue their en’mies,    and against them turn my hand. “Those who hate the LORD would cower,    and their doom would never end. But with finest wheat I’d feed you,    honey from the rock I’d send.”

