1    Save, O God, by your great name, vindicate me, blot out blame. Lord, my earnest praying hear, to my pleading words give ear. 

2    Strangers are attacking me: from their violence set me free. From their life the Lord they’ve banned, but to me God is at hand. 

3    God, the Lord, sustains my soul; evil deeds back on them roll; ’gainst my foes the Lord defends, and my praise to him ascends. 

I give thanks unto your name, it is good beyond all blame: God delivered me from grief, I now celebrate relief!

