1   We give you thanks, O  God, because your name is near. All speak of your majestic deeds; your voice we also hear: 

2   “I choose the  appointed time; I judge with justice sure. When earth and all its people quake, its pillars I secure. 

3   ““Boast not!” I tell the proud; the wicked I address: “Do not lift up your heads with pride, or speak with haughtiness”.” 

No one in all the earth    can truly give renown. God is the judge; he raises one    and puts another down.

God’s works I will proclaim,    and Jacob’s God I’ll praise. The wicked’s strength I will destroy;    the righteous I will raise.

The LORD’s hand holds a cup    with wine of powerful blend; he pours it out, and wicked ones    must drink it to the end.

