LORD, listen to my prayer, And hear my cry for aid. Hide not your face from me, For I am so afraid. Incline your ear to me in need; And, when I call, be swift to heed. 

Like smoke my days are gone; My bones are burned away. My appetite is lost; My heart is parched like hay. Because of my incessant groans I am no more than skin and bones. 

I'm like a desert owl, An owl midst tumbled stone, Or bird upon a roof I lie awake, alone. My foes revile me all day long; My haters mock my name in song. 

