1    How good it is to thank the LORD, to praise your name with tuneful chord, to show your love with morning light and tell your faithfulness each night. Yes, it is good your praise to sing, and all our sweetest music bring. 

2    O LORD, my song with joy expands before the wonders of your hands. How great the works that you have wrought; how deep, O LORD, your every thought! You make me glad; I sing your praise for all your wondrous works and ways. 

3    Though as the grass the wicked grow, those evildoers do not know the endless ruin they will see. But God will reign eternally. All foes will fall before his might; the wicked shall be put to flight. 

O LORD, you have exalted me with royal strength and dignity. With your anointing I am blest; your grace and favour on me rest. My eyes have seen the wicked die; my ears have heard their hopeless cry.

The righteous all will flourish well and in the house of God will dwell. They will be planted like a tree, will still in old age fruitful be. the LORD our God is upright, just; he is my Rock; in him I trust.

