1    Hear, O Israel's shepherd, hear us; Joseph like a flock you lead. You who are enthroned in glory shine upon us in our need. 

2    Shine on Benjamin, Manasseh, and for Ephraim rouse your might! Turn us once again towards you; come and save us, give us light! 

3    O LORD God, the Lord Almighty, how long will your anger smoke, making void your people's prayers, so that all your enemies mock? 

You have fed us bread of sorrow;    tears in plenty we must shed. We are now before our neighbours    humbled and discredited.  Look on us, O God Almighty;    let us see your glory bright. Turn us once again towards you;    come and save us, give us light!  Once you brought a vine from Egypt,    drove out kings with mighty hand, set the vine in ground made ready;    it took root and filled the land.  So its branches clothed the mountains,    shading every cedar tree, spreading from the great Euphrates    to the mighty western Sea.  Why did you break down its fences,    so that all may pluck its fruit? Creatures of the field devour it;    wild boars tear it from the root. 

Turn to us, O God Almighty,    look and see from heaven above! Tend this vine your hand has planted    and the son you raised in love.  See your vine cut down and withered,    and its branches burned with fire; your rebuke has crushed your people,    and they perish in your ire.  Let your hand be placed in blessing    on the man at your right hand— On the son of man you’ve chosen,    whom alone you caused to stand.  Then we will not wander from you,    turning from you to our shame. Strengthen us, revive and heal us;    then we’ll call upon your name.  Look on us, LORD God Almighty;    let us see your glory bright. Turn us once again towards you;    come and save us, give us light! 

