1   The trespass of the wicked man most plainly testifies that fear of God’s most holy name is not before his eyes. 

2   He views himself with blind conceit, his sinfulness denies. He speaks with evil and deceit, no longer good or wise. 

3   In bed he plots his evil ways; he schemes throughout the night, as he commits himself to sin, rejecting what is right. 

Your steadfast love is great, O LORD; it reaches heaven high. Your faithfulness is wonderful, extending to the sky.    

To those who know you as their God, your steadfast love impart; maintain your righteousness to those of pure and upright heart.  

Your righteousness is very great, like mountains high and steep; your justice is like ocean depths. Both man and beast you keep.      

How precious is your steadfast love! What confidence it brings! Both high and low find shelter in the shadow of your wings.    

They feast within your house, and drink from streams of your delight. For with you is the source of life; in your light we see light.    

Let not the ruthless foot of pride approach and threaten me, nor let the hand of wickedness force me to turn and flee.    

See where these evildoers lie, who righteousness despise! Thrown down are they, and there they stay, unable to arise.

