1   O LORD, in your strength how the king is exultant! How great is his joy in the triumphs you bring! To him you have granted his heart’s deepest longing; you answered the plea from the lips of the king. 

2   You welcomed him richly with blessings of goodness; a crown of fine gold you have placed on his head. He asked you for life, and you gave him it freely – abundance of days, that his years should not end. 

3   Through triumphs you gave his renown is exalted, and you have bestowed on him splendour and grace. You surely have granted him blessings eternal; you filled him with joy by the light of your face. (cont) 3   For the king puts his trust in the LORD high above; unshaken he stands through the LORD’s steadfast love. 

