1   I waited long upon the LORD; he heard my cry and turned to me. He raised me from the slimy pit and from the mire he pulled me free. He set my feet on solid rock, a place to stand both firm and broad. He put a new song in my mouth, a joyful hymn of praise to God. 

2   Many will look with godly fear and on the LORD alone rely. Blessed are they who trust the LORD, who shun the proud and gods that lie. The wonders you have done,O LORD, how many and how great they are! Your plans for us are far beyond our power to number or declare. 

3   You did not ask that calves or goats be brought as sacrifice for sin, but you have opened up my ears; you did not seek burnt offering. Then I declared, “LORD, I have come; it’s written of me in the scroll. I want to do your will, my God; your law is in my heart and soul.” 

Do not withhold your mercy, LORD; surround your servant constantly with your great love and faithfulness, for many troubles threaten me. My sins have overtaken me; they’re more than hairs upon my head. My heart within me fails for grief; I cannot see the way ahead.

In the assembly when it met your justice I proclaimed abroad. I did not seal my lips at all;  you know all this about me, LORD. I did not hide within my heart your saving grace and righteousness; in the assembly I proclaimed your steadfast love and faithfulness.

But let all those who seek your face be joyful in you all their days; let those who love salvation say, “Exalted be the LORD always!” Yet I am poor and in great need; LORD, think on me, I humbly pray. You are my Saviour and my help; come, O my God! Do not delay.

Be pleased, O LORD, to rescue me; O LORD, come quickly to my aid. May all who seek to take my life with shame and turmoil be repaid. May all who plot my overthrow turn back, disgraced, the way they came. May those who mock me to my face become appalled at their own shame.

