1    I cried in trouble to the LORD, and he has answered me. From lying lips and crafty tongue, O LORD, my soul set free. What shall be given you, false tongue? What added to your doom? Sharp arrows of a mighty man, and redhot coals of broom. 

2    Alas for me that I sojourn so long in Meshech's land; that I have made my dwelling where the tents of Kedar stand. Too long my soul has made its home with those who peace abhor. I am for peace; but when I speak, they ready are for war. 



