1    LORD, chasten not in anger, nor in your wrath rebuke me. Give me your healing word. My soul and body languish; I wait for you in anguish. How long, how long, O LORD? 

2    Turn to me now, uphold me; for your love’s sake restore me. O save me by your grace. For death ends all remembrance; it wraps the tongue in silence. How can the dead sing praise? 

3    Pain and distress o’erwhelm me, I cry all night for mercy, my bed is wet with tears. My eyes can weep no longer; my enemies seem stronger, my awful foes and fears. 

