1    On the holy mountains the Lord laid His foundation. He loves the gates  of Zion far above all the dwelling places in Jacob's habitation. Glorious things are spoken of God's city that I love. Rahab, Ethiopia and also Babylon, Tyre and Philistia in her belong. And join the throng. 

2    Zion, blessed Zion, by God himself established, how blessed are the born again that you have known. There will be salvation for ev'ry tribe and nation, and the Lord shall count them all to be His very own. Flutes and instruments will lead the throng and they will sing, All the joys within me from Zion spring. From Zion spring! 



