1           Blessed is the man, the man who does not walk in the counsel of the ungodly, blessed is that man. He who rejects the way, rejects the way of sin and who turns away from scoffing, blessed is that man. But his delight by day and night is the law of GOD Almighty. Blessed is the man, the man who does not walk in the counsel of the ungodly, blessed is that man! 

2           He is like a tree, a tree that flourishes being planted by the water, blessed is that man! He will bring forth fruit, his leaf will wither not, for in all he does he prospers, blessed is that man. For his delight by day and night is the law of GOD Almighty. 

3           godly are not so, for they are like the chaff which the wind blows clean away, godly are not so. godly will not stand upon the judgment day nor belong to GOD’s own people, godly will not stand. But GOD knows way of righteous men and ungodly ways will perish. 

