1    O Lord of hosts, how lovely thy tabernacles are; for them my heart is yearning in banishment afar. My soul is longing, fainting, thy sacred courts to see; my heart and flesh are crying, O living God for thee. 

2    Beneath thy care the sparrow finds place for peaceful rest; to keep her young in safety the swallow finds a nest; then, Lord, my king almighty, thy love will shelter me; beside thy holy altar my dwellingplace shall be. 

3    Blest they who dwell in Zion, whose joy and strength thou art; forever they will praise thee, thy ways are in their heart. Though tried, their tears like showers shall fill the springs of peace, and all the way to Zion their strength shall still increase. 

In thy blest courts to worship,    my God, a single day is better than a thousand    while far from thee I stray. Though in a lowly station,    the service of my Lord I choose above all pleasures    that sinful ways afford.  A sun and shield forever    is God, the Lord most high; to those who walk uprightly    no good will he deny. His saints, his grace receiving,    shall soon his glory see; O Lord of hosts, most blessed    are they that trust in thee. 

Lord, God, of hosts, in mercy    my supplication hear; almighty and all-faithful,   our fathers’ God, give ear. Our shield and great defender,    no longer hide thy face, but look upon thy servant,    anointed by thy grace.

