O LORD, why do you stand remote and stay so far away? Why do you hide yourself from us when trouble comes our way? 

The wicked in his arrogance hunts down the weak and poor, who in the snares that he has set are caught and held secure. 

About the cravings of his heart he speaks with boastful word; he praises people filled with greed while he reviles the LORD. 

His victims by his strength are crushed; his prey collapse and fall. He thinks, “God does not notice it; he does not see at all.”   Arise, LORD God, lift up your hand; do not forget the poor. Why does the wicked say of God, “My conduct he’ll ignore”?   But you, O God, do see such wrong and you will bring redress. The victim puts his trust in you; you help the fatherless.   LORD, break the wicked person’s power and call him to account for all the evil which he thought would never be found out.   The LORD will ever reign as King; his throne will always stand. The heathen nations of the world will perish from his land.   O LORD, the needy ones’ desire you answer from on high; you give encouragement to them and listen to their cry.   For you defend the fatherless and those who are oppressed, so that from fear of mortal man the helpless may have rest. 

The wicked does not seek the LORD because he is so proud, and in his inmost thoughts there is no room at all for God.   His ways are always prosperous; he strikes a haughty pose. He keeps his distance from your laws; he sneers at all his foes.   He reassures himself and says, “No threat will topple me – I will be happy evermore; from trouble I’ll be free.”   

