1    You rulers, do you know what justice is? Among mankind do you judge uprightly? No, you devise injustice in your hearts, and on the earth you mete out cruelty. 

2    Even from birth the wicked go astray and from the womb untruthfully they speak; their wayward thoughts well up within their hearts, and havoc with their lying words they wreak. 

3    Their poison’s like the venom of a snake; they’re like a cobra that has closed its ear – however great the charmer’s skill may be, it pays no heed because it does not hear. 

