1   In wrath do not rebuke me, LORD, or in your anger chasten me. Your arrows deeply pierce my soul; your hand lies on me heavily. 

2   Because your anger rests on me, my body has no health within; there is no soundness in my bones, because you judge me for my sin. 

3   My guilt has overwhelmed my soul; its burden is a crushing weight. My wounds are foul and festering, because my foolishness is great. 

My enemies who seek my life with cunning set their snares for me; my foes conspire to do me harm, and all day long plot treachery.

My heart beats wildly, strength has failed, the light has faded from my eye. My friends and neighbours keep away; they see my wounds and then pass by.

I’m feeble and completely crushed; in anguish of my heart I groan. LORD, my desires before you lie; to you my sighing is well known.

I am bowed down, I am brought low, and I go mourning all the day. My back is filled with searing pain, and my whole body wastes away.

O LORD, do not abandon me; do not be far from me, my God. Come quickly to deliver me because you are my Saviour, LORD.

11

I’m like the deaf, who cannot hear, and like the mute, who cannot cry. I’m like a man who hears no sound, whose mouth can offer no reply.

I wait for you, O LORD my God; and you, O LORD, will answer me. I prayed to you, “If my foot slips, let them not gloat exultantly.”

My foes are vigorous and strong; and many hate me wrongfully. My good with evil they repay; when I seek good, they slander me.

Indeed I am about to fall; my pain is ever deep within. I must confess iniquity, and I am troubled by my sin.

