LORD, our Lord, thy glorious name all thy wondrous works proclaim; in the heavens with radiant signs evermore thy glory shines. How great thy name! LORD, our Lord, in all the earth, how great thy name! Thine the name of matchless worth, excellent in all the earth; how great thy name! 

Infant lips thou dost ordain wrath and vengeance to restrain; weakest means fulfil thy will, mighty enemies to still. 

Moon and stars in shining height nightly tell their maker’s might; when thy wondrous heavens I scan, then I know how weak is man. 

What is man that he should be loved and visited by thee, raised to an exalted height, crowned with honour in thy sight!    How great thy name!   With dominion crowned he stands o’er the creatures of thy hands; all to him subjection yield in the sea and air and field.    How great thy name!

