 1    Do good  to me and I will live; your servant will obey your word. Open my with eyes that I may see great wonders in your law, O LORD. 

2    I am a stranger on the earth; do not hide your commands from me. Consumed longing is my soul,  because your laws I yearn to see. 



Though rulers plot to harm my name, I'll meditate on your decree. Your statutes are my great delight, for they are counsellors to me.

