1    Great is the LORD our God, and greatly to be praised. Upon a hill God’s city stands in glorious beauty raised – his holy mountain high, the city of our King, the joy of all the earth below. In praise of God we sing. 

2    God makes his city strong by living in her halls. When kings join forces and advance, they marvel at her walls. They stand and look amazed in terror and alarm; as anguish grips like labour pains, they see their certain harm. 

3    For just as God destroyed the ships of Tarshish old, by east wind shattered, so he crushed those kings who were so bold! As in the past we heard, now we have seen it so: the city of the LORD of hosts no one can overthrow. 

Within your temple, LORD, in that most holy place, we on your lovingkindness dwell, the wonders of your grace. Your people sing your praise where’er your name is known;  by every deed your hand has worked your righteousness is shown.   Let Zion now rejoice and all her people sing; let them with thankfulness proclaim the judgments of their King. Mount Zion’s walls behold, about her ramparts go, and number all the lofty towers that guard her from the foe.   Observe her palaces, mark her defenses well, that to your children following her glories you may tell. For God as our own God forever will abide, and till life’s journey close in death will be our faithful guide. 

