1   Come! Vindicate me, O my God! Against this nation plead my cause! Deliver me from wicked foes and hypocrites who break your laws. 

2   You are  my stronghold and my God; why then have you rejected me? Why must I go about in grief, downtrodden by the enemy? 

3   O send your light forth and your truth! Let them direct me in your grace and bring me to your holy hill, into your sacred dwellingplace. 

