1    Sing to the LORD, sing his praise, all you peoples; new be your song as new honours you pay. Sing of his majesty, praise him forever, show his salvation from day to day. 

2    Tell of his wondrous works, tell of his glory, till through the nations his name is revered. Praise and exalt him, for he is almighty; God over all, let the LORD be feared. 

3    Vain are the idols and gods of the nations; God made the heavens, and his glory they tell. Splendour and majesty shine out before him; glory and strength in his temple dwell. 

Give unto God most high glory and honour;    come with your offerings and humbly draw near. Worship the LORD in all beauty and splendour;    tremble before him with godly fear.  Say to the nations, “The LORD reigns forever.”    Earth is established as he did decree. Righteous and just is the king of the nations,    judging the peoples with equity.  Let heaven and earth be glad; oceans, be joyful;    forest and field, exultation express. For God is coming, the judge of the nations,    coming to judge in his righteousness.

