1    Almighty LORD God, who judges the earth, arise, give the proud just what they deserve. How long will they boast and in arrogance mock, oppressing the people you take as your flock? 

2    They say God will not observe what they do, that he will not see the sins they pursue. The widows they murder, the fatherless snare; and strangers they kill, thinking God does not care. 

3    You fools, our God knows how senseless you are! For he who made all can see near and far. Is God who first fashioned your eye and your ear unable to see you, unable to hear? 

The people you teach and discipline, LORD, are happy and blest to learn from your word. For you grant relief to all those in despair, allowing them peace till the wicked are snared.  O LORD, you will not abandon your own nor ever forsake them nor leave them alone. Your justice will dawn for all those who do right, and those who are upright will follow its light.  Who helps me to fight sin’s mighty offence? Who will be my shield and my sure defence? Unless God had helped me when evil oppressed, I too would have slipped into silence and death.

Whenever I fall, I pleadingly cry; then your loving hand, LORD, holds me up high. If my heart should doubt and be filled with despair, your comfort brings joy, and I know that you care.  Corruption cannot be allied with you; injustice cannot be legal or true. For you, LORD, will never conspire with our foes who gather together, increasing our woes.  The LORD is my rock, invincible, strong; he punishes all who perpetrate wrong. Our God will repay them for sins they have sown, but he will have mercy and love for his own.

