1    O God, please listen to my prayer; do not ignore my plea. My anxious thoughts make me distraught; O hear and answer me. 

2    I’m troubled by the voice of foes, by their malicious stare; for they bring suffering to me – their hatred I must bear. 

3   Within me anguish grips my heart; death’s terrors have come near. I tremble and am terrified; I’m overwhelmed by fear. 

“O that I, like a dove, had wings! Then I would fly away and be at rest; I’d flee from here and in the desert stay.   “Then would I to my hiding-place for refuge take my flight, far from the raging of the storm and from the tempest’s might.”

But you, O God, will bring them down – those evil, wicked men – into the pit of death’s decay forever to remain.  Bloodthirsty and deceitful men will not live half their days; but as for me, my confidence will rest in you always.

But it is you, my closest friend, a man whom I well know; we once enjoyed sweet fellowship, as to God’s house we’d go.  Let death come on my enemies and take them by surprise; may they go to the grave alive, for evil in them lies.  But as for me, I call to God; the LORD will save me now. At evening, morning and at noon, in prayer to him I bow.  Distressed, I cry – he hears my voice. He ransoms me unharmed from battle waged by many foes, who are against me armed.   

This man attacks his loyal friends and breaks his solemn word. As smooth as butter is his speech, but in his heart’s a sword.  O cast your burden on the LORD, and he will care for you; he’ll never let the righteous fall, but bring him safely through. 

